screene.com 2014-04-08

# Screene.com- Privacy Policy

We respect the privacy of our visitors and surfers. We do not sell, barter or exchange email addresses you give us when sending a greeting unless a visitor has given us explicit permission to do so. 

**Limitations on privacy:**  
We reserve the right to provide information if we think - correctly or incorrectly and reasonably or unreasonably - that our screensavers, wallpapers and/or ecards are being used in violation of our terms of use, including, but not limited to, being used in any illegal, harmful, threatening or anti-social activity. 

We try to protect your privacy, but you must please understand that any use of the Internet or of email creates the possibility that someone could access the data transmitted. There is always some risk on the web that personal information might be accessed and privacy cannot be guaranteed. 

**Affiliates, Advertisers and Others:**   
Before providing information to any party other than screene.com or any of its sites, you should check their privacy policy, as they are third parties. We may use third party TAF services for the function of sending pages. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices utilized by any other sites, linked by us. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

For any queries, contact us.
